Register of the Vladimir Pribylovskiĭ collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Writings by Others, 1985-2002
  - Materials published by the Panorama Information and Research Center think tank, 1985-2000
    - Kozhevnikova, G., and K. Listratov, "Arbitrazhnye sudy Rossii,", 2000 (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - Manulian, S., "Respublika Armeniia: organy vlasti,", 2000 (Box-folder 110: 1-3)
    - Mikhailovskaia, E., "Krym, sbornik materialov,", 1992 (Box-folder 75: 3)
    - Mikhailovskaia, E., "Ukraina: politicheskie partii i organizatsii,", 1992 (Box-folder 68: 3)
    - Mitrokhin, N., and V. Ponomarev, "Informatsionnaia svodka po Turkmenistanu,", 1996 (Box-folder 105: 9)
    - Mitrokhin, N., and V. Ponomarev, "Uzbekistan: politicheskaia, ekonomicheskaia i religioznaia situatsiia,", 1996 (Box-folder 75: 6, Box-folder 105: 10)
    - Mukhin, A., and A. Glubotskii, "Moskva i Moskovskaia oblast': struktura vlasti,", 1995 (Box-folder 70: 18)
    - Muzeev, T., and Z. Todua, "Novaia Checheno-Ingushetia,", 1992 (Box-folder 75: 4)
    - Nikol'skii, V., "Slang: Dictionary of Contemporary Russian,", 1993 (Box-folder 117: 9-10)
    - Ovchinnikov, V., "Na pereput'iakh Rossii,", 1997 (Box-folder 66: 1-3)
    - Polenov, V., "Vospominaniia,", 1985 (Box-folder 65: 10)
    - Shukurov, S. and P. Shukurov, "Tsentral'naia Aziia (opyt istorii dukha),", 1996 (Box-folder 75: 5)
    - Tiukov, N., "15 nezavisimukh respublik,", 1992-1994 (Box-folder 68: 8, Box-folder 99: 8, Box-folder 107: 6)
    - Todua, Z., "Azerbaidzhan segodnia,", 1995 (Box-folder 106: 1)
    - Toropov, D., "Spravochnik novykh partii i obshchestvennykh organizatsii Tatarstana,", 1992 (Box-folder 68: 5)
    - Toropov, D., "Tatarstan: Political Aspect,", 1993 (Box-folder 75: 2)
    - Verkhovskii, A., "Sredniaia Aziia i Kazakhstan,", 1992 (Box-folder 50: 2)
  - Berezovskii, V. N. and V. V. Cherviakov, "100 partiinykh liderov Rossii," RAY-Korporatsiia, 1993 (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - Bogdanova, Milana, "Samizdat i politicheskie organizatsii Sibiri i Dal'nego Vostoka," "Samizdatskaia periodika Sibiri i Dal'nego Vostoka," Institut gumanitarno- politicheskikh issledovanii, Moskva, 1991 (Box-folder 50: 6, Box-folder 107: 1)
  - D'iakov, N., "Mechenye," Moskva, 1996 (Box-folder 75: 7-10)
  - Kliamkin, I., E. Petrenko, and D. Chubukov, "Sotsial'no-politicheskoe pole partii i dvizhenii," Fond "Obshchestvennoe mnenie," Moskva, 1992 (Box-folder 70: 22)
  - Koval'chuk-Koval', I., "Svidanie s pamiat'iu," typescrpt, incomplete, circa 1996 (Box-folder 122: 10)
  - Kuzin, V., Presledovanie inakomysliashchikh v SShA: Delo # 88-00243-A E.D. Va. "SShA protiv Lindona Larusha i dr., Moskovskoe biuro "Zashchita prav cheloveka bez granits," Moskva, 1995 (Box-folder 75: 14)
  - Szerepka, L. "Rosyjskie ugrupowania nacjonalistyczne," Warzaw, 1995 (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - Zakatov, A., "Arkheograficheskoe osvoenie istochnikov po istorii partii mladorossov, 1923-1941 g.g.," diplomnaia rabota, Rossiiskii gosudarstvennyi gumanitarnyi universitet, Moskva, 1995 (Box-folder 50: 7)
  - Zotova, Z., and G. Tafaev, "Politicheskie partii Rossii. Vybory-95," Chuvashskii gosudarstvennyi universitet, Cheboksary, 1996 (Box-folder 117: 5-8)
- Clippings and internet printouts, 1996-2006 (Box-folder 51: 5-10, Box-folder 103: 10-12, Box-folder 104: 14-15)
  Russian newspaper clippings and press releases relating to political, social, and economic conditions in Russia.
- Printed matter, 1989-2004
  Includes newspapers, journals, and brochures relating to election campaigns and other social, economic, and political conditions in Russia.
  - General, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 55: 2-8, Box-folder 57: 5, Box-folder 119: 1-2)
    Includes brochures, bulletins, programs, and leaflets.
  - Bulletins, 1989-2002
    - Agentstvo novostei i informatsii (ANI). Moskva, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 67: 14-15, Box-folder 68: 1-2)
    - "Federal'noe Sobranie Rossiskoi Federatsii," no. 5, 1994 (Box-folder 121: 13)
    - "Gosudarstvennaia Duma: stenogramma zasedanii," nos. 179, 180, 190, 191, 195, 243, 248, 251, 255, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 121: 10-12)
    - "Iaponiia o sebe i mire," daidzhest, no. 2, Aktsionernoe obshchestvo "Iaponiia segodnia," Moskva, 1992 (Box-folder 121: 15)
    - "Materialy k voprosam o gosudarstvennom plane ekonomicheskogo i sotsial'nogo razvitiia SSSR i o gosudarstvennom biudzhete SSSR na 1990 god,", 1989 (Box-folder 92: 16)
    - "N. B!" biulleten' ekspertov Parlamentskoi koalitsii reform "Nota Bene,", 1992 (Box-folder 122: 8)
    - "Parlamentskaia nedeliia," informatsionnyi biulleten', 1992-1993 (Box-folder 121: 5-9)
    - "Soveshchanie-seminar predsedatelei raiionnykh Sovetov narodnykh deputatov Tsentral'nogo i Volgo-Viatskogo raionov Rossiiskoi Federatsii," stenograficheskii otchet, 1993 (Box-folder 121: 14)
    - Sessii Verkhovnogo Soveta Rossiskoi Federatsii, 1991-1993
      - IV sessiia, no. 25, and dnevnik, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 121: 1)
      - V sessiia, nos. 27-28, and dnevnik, 1992 (Box-folder 121: 2)
      - VI sessiia, nos. 7, 17, 19, 41, 51, 52, 1993 (Box-folder 121: 3-4)
    - S"ezdy Narodnykh Deputatov Rossiskoi Federatsii, 1990-1993
      - General, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 122: 4-6)
      - I s"ezd, no. 34, 1990 (Box-folder 119: 7)
      - II vneocherednoi s"ezd, nos. 1-9, 13-15, 20-27, 1990 (Box-folder 119: 3, Box-folder 122: 1-2)
      - III vneocherednoi s"ezd, nos. 9-13, 1991 (Box-folder 122: 3)
      - V vheocherednoi s"ezd, nos. 1-22, 1991 (Box-folder 119: 4-6)
      - VI s"ezd, nos. 1, 5-26, 1992 (Box-folder 119: 8-12, Box-folder 120: 1-2)
      - VII s"ezd, nos. 1-22, 1992 (Box-folder 120: 3-7)
      - VIII vneocherednoi s"ezd, nos. 1-7, 1993 (Box-folder 120: 8-9)
      - IX vneocherednoi s"ezd, nos. 1-7, and stenogramma, 1993 (Box-folder 120: 10-11)
  - Newspapers, 1989-2003
    - Avtorskoe pravo, Saratovskoe gubernskoe obozrenie, ezhenedel'nik, nos. 1-7, 11-20, 30, Saratov, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 1)
    - Delo, politicheskoe obozrenie, ezhenedel'nik, nos. 36-37, Samara, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 2)
    - Khronika, obshchestvenno-politicheskaia gazeta izbiratelei, nos. 18-19, Moskva, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 3)
    - Krest'ianin, Rossiiskaia gazeta, nos. 31, 36, Rostov-na- Dony, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 4)
    - Krest'ianskaia gazeta, izdanie fermerov Rossii, nos. 15, 19, Perm', 1993 (Box-folder 125: 5)
    - Kto est' kto / Who's Who, nos. 7-9, Moskva, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 6)
    - Kuranty, no. 185, Moskva, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 7)
    - Kur'er, ezhenedel'nik, no. 44, Moskva, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 8)
    - Moia gazeta, nos. 10-11, Samara, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 9)
    - Na boevom postu, gazeta Moskovskogo okruga protibozdushnoi oborony, no. 101, Moscow, Moskva, 1993 (Box-folder 125: 10)
    - Nasha Strana (Nuestro Pais), nos. 2701-2702, 2705-2708, 2732-2733, 2736, 2738-2739, Buenos Aires, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 55: 16)
    - Nashe Otechestvo, nos. 25, 27-28, Sankt-Peterburg, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 55: 12)
    - Panorama, obzor problem obshchestvennoi zhizni, Nos. 1-12 (1989), 4-10 (1990), 1 (1994), 1 (1995), Moskva, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 65: 11-13, Box-folder 87: 9-10)
    - Russkoe delo, nezavisimaia gazeta, nos. 1-3 (1991), 1-6 (1992), 1-3, 21 (1993), Sankt-Peterburg, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 125: 12)
  - Magazines, 1992-2004
    - "Forum, prilozhenie k gazete Vedomosti; investitsii v Krasnoiarskii ktai," Moskva, 2004 (Box-folder 125: 11)
    - Kommersantie, analiticheskii ezhenedel'nik izdatel'skogo doma "Ie," nos. 8, 10-13, 15, 17, 18, 1995 (Box-folder 65: 2-4)
    - SEA: SocEco Agency Sotsial'no-ekologicheskii soiuz, Moskva, 1992 (Box-folder 118: 3-5)
    - Vedomocti "Forum": investiysii v Krasnoiarskii krai, Moskva, 2004 May (Box-folder 123: 11)
    - Vek XX i mir: khronika tekushchikh sobytii, Moskva, 1993 October (Box-folder 118: 2)